// Array de preguntas MEDIO

const preguntas_medium = [
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "1",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 3 + 4?",
    "respuesta": "7",
    "incorrecta1": "5",
    "incorrecta2": "8",
    "incorrecta3": "6",
    "objectFit": "fill",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "2",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 10 - 5?",
    "respuesta": "5",
    "incorrecta1": "3",
    "incorrecta2": "7",
    "incorrecta3": "4",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "3",
    "categoria": "Multiplicaciones",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 2 x 3?",
    "respuesta": "6",
    "incorrecta1": "5",
    "incorrecta2": "7",
    "incorrecta3": "4",
    "objectFit": "contain",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "4",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 5 + 2?",
    "respuesta": "7",
    "incorrecta1": "6",
    "incorrecta2": "8",
    "incorrecta3": "4",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "5",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 8 - 3?",
    "respuesta": "5",
    "incorrecta1": "4",
    "incorrecta2": "6",
    "incorrecta3": "7",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "6",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 4 + 3?",
    "respuesta": "7",
    "incorrecta1": "6",
    "incorrecta2": "8",
    "incorrecta3": "5",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "7",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 9 - 4?",
    "respuesta": "5",
    "incorrecta1": "3",
    "incorrecta2": "6",
    "incorrecta3": "7",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "8",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 6 + 2?",
    "respuesta": "8",
    "incorrecta1": "7",
    "incorrecta2": "9",
    "incorrecta3": "5",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "9",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 - 2?",
    "respuesta": "5",
    "incorrecta1": "3",
    "incorrecta2": "6",
    "incorrecta3": "4",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "10",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 8 + 3?",
    "respuesta": "11",
    "incorrecta1": "10",
    "incorrecta2": "12",
    "incorrecta3": "9",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "11",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 12 - 5?",
    "respuesta": "7",
    "incorrecta1": "6",
    "incorrecta2": "8",
    "incorrecta3": "4",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "12",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 9 + 2?",
    "respuesta": "11",
    "incorrecta1": "10",
    "incorrecta2": "12",
    "incorrecta3": "8",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "13",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 15 - 7?",
    "respuesta": "8",
    "incorrecta1": "6",
    "incorrecta2": "9",
    "incorrecta3": "10",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "14",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 7 + 6?",
    "respuesta": "13",
    "incorrecta1": "12",
    "incorrecta2": "14",
    "incorrecta3": "15",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "15",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 20 - 9?",
    "respuesta": "11",
    "incorrecta1": "10",
    "incorrecta2": "12",
    "incorrecta3": "13",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "16",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 8 + 5?",
    "respuesta": "13",
    "incorrecta1": "12",
    "incorrecta2": "14",
    "incorrecta3": "15",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "17",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 25 - 12?",
    "respuesta": "13",
    "incorrecta1": "11",
    "incorrecta2": "14",
    "incorrecta3": "15",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "18",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 9 + 7?",
    "respuesta": "16",
    "incorrecta1": "15",
    "incorrecta2": "17",
    "incorrecta3": "18",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "19",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 30 - 14?",
    "respuesta": "16",
    "incorrecta1": "15",
    "incorrecta2": "17",
    "incorrecta3": "18",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "20",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 12 + 8?",
    "respuesta": "20",
    "incorrecta1": "18",
    "incorrecta2": "22",
    "incorrecta3": "24",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "21",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 40 - 19?",
    "respuesta": "21",
    "incorrecta1": "20",
    "incorrecta2": "22",
    "incorrecta3": "23",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "22",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 15 + 9?",
    "respuesta": "24",
    "incorrecta1": "22",
    "incorrecta2": "25",
    "incorrecta3": "26",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "23",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 50 - 22?",
    "respuesta": "28",
    "incorrecta1": "26",
    "incorrecta2": "30",
    "incorrecta3": "32",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "24",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 18 + 6?",
    "respuesta": "24",
    "incorrecta1": "20",
    "incorrecta2": "22",
    "incorrecta3": "26",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "25",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 60 - 35?",
    "respuesta": "25",
    "incorrecta1": "20",
    "incorrecta2": "30",
    "incorrecta3": "40",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "26",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 25 + 9?",
    "respuesta": "34",
    "incorrecta1": "30",
    "incorrecta2": "35",
    "incorrecta3": "40",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "27",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 80 - 42?",
    "respuesta": "38",
    "incorrecta1": "35",
    "incorrecta2": "40",
    "incorrecta3": "45",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "28",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 30 + 25?",
    "respuesta": "55",
    "incorrecta1": "50",
    "incorrecta2": "60",
    "incorrecta3": "65",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "29",
    "categoria": "Restas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 100 - 57?",
    "respuesta": "43",
    "incorrecta1": "40",
    "incorrecta2": "45",
    "incorrecta3": "50",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  },
  {
    "numeroPregunta": "30",
    "categoria": "Sumas",
    "pregunta": "¿Cuánto es 40 + 30?",
    "respuesta": "70",
    "incorrecta1": "60",
    "incorrecta2": "80",
    "incorrecta3": "90",
    "objectFit": "cover",
  }
];
